Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999
  - Subseries II:B: Lillian Roberts Associate Director Records, 1951-1983.
    - New York City HHC: Training Program for Billing/Collecting, 1971-1972; cuid4883 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Tripartite Task Force on Potential Additional Sources of Revenue and Decentralization, Jul 1976; cuid4884 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Basic Education Program, 1970; cuid4885 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - New York City Housing and Development Administration (HDA), undated, 1977-1978; cuid4886 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - New York City HDA: Community Liaison Workers (Local 371), 1977-1979; cuid4887 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - New York City HDA: Support Service Contracts, 1978-1979; cuid4888 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - New York City Human Resources Administration, 1976-1979; cuid4889 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - New York City Juvenile Justice Agency, 1979; cuid4890 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - New York City Manual of Personnel Policies, undated; cuid4891 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - New York City Medical School Proposal, Jun 1972-Oct 1973; cuid4892 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - New York City Medical School Proposal, Feb 1974-Jul 1975; cuid4893 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York City Office of Labor Relations, 1973-1975; cuid4894 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - New York City Unemployed and Welfare Council, 1978; cuid4895 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - New York State Advisory Council on Substance Abuse, 1976-1980; cuid4896 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - New York State Department of Civil Service: Title and Salary Plan I, 1968; cuid4897 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - New York State Department of Civil Service: Title and Salary Plan II, 1968; cuid4898 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - New York State Department of Mental Hygiene: Inventory of Inservice Training Courses, 1966; cuid4899 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - New York State Division of Substance Abuse Services, 1980; cuid4900 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - New York State Employment and Training Council, 1979-1980; cuid4901 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - New York Urban Coalition, 1980-1981; cuid4902 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - New York Urban Coalition: Health Manpower Committee, 1969-1970; cuid4903 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - North Brooklyn Hospital Training Project, 1972-1974; cuid4904 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - North Brooklyn Hospital Training Project (Woodhull Hospital): Proposal to Train Community Residents for Professional Positions, 1972-1973; cuid4905 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1973-1974; cuid4906 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1975; cuid4907 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1976; cuid4908 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Nurse's Aide to Licensed Practical Nurse (LPN) Upgrading Program, 1967-1968; cuid4909 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program, Jan 1969-May 1969; cuid4910 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program, Jun 1969-Dec 1969; cuid4911 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction for Blood Pressure, 1968; cuid4912 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction on Vocational Adjustment I, 1968; cuid4913 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction on Vocational Adjustment II, 1968; cuid4914 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Printed Material and Publicity, 1967-1969; cuid4915 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, 1967; cuid4916 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, 1967-1968; cuid4917 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Feb 1968-Jun 1968; cuid4918 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Jun 1968-Nov 1968; cuid4919 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Nov 1968-Apr 1969; cuid4920 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Apr 1969-Sep 1969; cuid4921 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Sep 1969-Dec 1969; cuid4922 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153, 1970; cuid4923 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Outside Activities, 1967-1971; cuid4924 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Personal Services Unit, 1970-1973; cuid4925 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Issues, 1969; cuid4926 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Issues, 1970-1972; cuid4927 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Personnel Issues, 1973; cuid4928 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Issues, 1974-1975; cuid4929 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Personnel Issues, 1976-1977; cuid4930 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1974-1976; cuid4931 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Pipeline Correspondence, 1971; cuid4932 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Political Action: Governor's Race (Rockefeller/Goldberg), 1970; cuid4933 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Productivity in City Agencies, 1972-1975; cuid4934 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Professional and Cultural Division: Monthly Staff Reports (Lubin, Castiglione, McCabe, Trotter, Hill, Shaplo, Baron), 1974-1975; cuid4935 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Public Service Employment Conference, 1973; cuid4936 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Queens General Hospital, 1976; cuid4937 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Reich, Chaim B., M.D., 1978; cuid4938 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: Health Services Mobility Study (HSMS) Plan of Work, 1968; cuid4939 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 1, "Train Practical Nurses to Become Registered Nurses" (Draft), 1968; cuid4940 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 1, "Train Practical Nurses to Become Registered Nurses: A Survey of the PN Point of View", 1968; cuid4941 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, Vol. 1, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals" (Draft)", 1969; cuid4942 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, Vol. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals" (Draft), 1969; cuid4943 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals, Volume 1", 1969; cuid4944 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals, Volume 2", 1969; cuid4945 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Reports Nos. 4 and 5, "Suggestions for Job and Curriculum Ladders in Health Center Ambulatory Care", 1972; cuid4946 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Second Progress Report, 1969; cuid4947 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 2, 1968; cuid4948 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 4, 1969; cuid4949 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 7, 1970; cuid4950 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report Nos. 8-9, 1970; cuid4951 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report Nos. 10-11, 1971-1972; cuid4952 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 2, "A Pre-Test Manual for Task Identification", 1968; cuid4953 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 4, "A Pre-Test Manual for Task Identification (Re-Test)", 1969; cuid4954 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 7, "A Re-Test Manual for Scaling Task Dimensions", 1970; cuid4955 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Roberts, Lillian, undated, 1971-1972, 1983; cuid4956 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Safety Issues, 1978-1979; cuid4957 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Safety Training, 1974-1975; cuid4958 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - School Decentralization, 1969; cuid4959 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - School Volunteer Program, 1976; cuid4960 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Apr 1974-Jun 1974; cuid4961 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Jul 1974-Feb 1975; cuid4962 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Mar 1975-Jul 1976; cuid4963 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Seaview Hospital, undated; cuid4964 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Segundo Ruiz Belvis Neighborhood Family Care Center, 1976; cuid4965 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Society for Advanced Medical Systems (SAMS), 1978; cuid4966 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches, undated, 1970-1971; cuid4967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches, 1972-1979; cuid4968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches: RAND Institute, Job Enrichment, 1973; cuid4969 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - State University of New York: Board of Trustees, 1979-1980; cuid4970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Stationary Firemen, 1971; cuid4971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Surgical Group Practice, Bellevue Hospital, 1971; cuid4972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1974-1976; cuid4973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1976-1978; cuid4974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1980; cuid4975 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Television Series, 1971; cuid4976 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Trade Union Committee to Restore Welfare, Medicaid, and School Lunch Cuts I, 1969-1970; cuid4977 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Trade Union Committee to Restore Welfare, Medicaid, and School Lunch Cuts II, 1969-1970; cuid4978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - United States Census, 1980; cuid4979 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: State Health Careers Councils and Committees Workshop, 1966; cuid4980 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1977; cuid4981 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Apr 1974-Sep 1974; cuid4982 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Oct 1974-Feb 1975; cuid4983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Mar 1975-Aug 1975; cuid4984 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Wildcat Services Corporation (Vera Institute of Justice), 1973-1977; cuid4985 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Women's Political Training Center, Hunter College: Advisory Board, 1977-1978; cuid4986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Woodhull Hospital, 1978; cuid4987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Woodhull Hospital: Mayor's Committee on Woodhull Report, 1978; cuid4988 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Work in America Institute: National Advisory Committee, 1979-1980; cuid4989 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Work Incentive Program (WIN) and New York Work Rules, ca.1970, 1971; cuid4990 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Work Relief Employment Program (WREP): Post-Certification, 1974-1975; cuid4991 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Workmen's Compensation, 1978-1979; cuid4992 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986
  - AFSCME Attorney's Conference, 1983; cuid4993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAE): Agreements, 1979; cuid4994 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1979-1981; cuid4995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1981; cuid4996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1982; cuid4997 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1982-1983; cuid4998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Constitution and Related Correspondence, undated, 1980-1984; cuid4999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 I, 1984; cuid5000 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 II, 1984; cuid5001 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 III, 1984; cuid5002 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37, Background Material, 1984; cuid5003 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Board of Education v. Vincent J. Byrne: Affidavits, 1975, 1977; cuid5004 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Background Materials, 1963-1976; cuid5005 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Court Papers, 1975-1977; cuid5006 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Exhibits, 1975-1977; cuid5007 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Memoranda and Correspondence, 1975-1977; cuid5008 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Notes, 1977; cuid5009 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts I, 1976-1977; cuid5010 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts II, 1976-1977; cuid5011 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts III, 1976-1977; cuid5012 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts IV, 1976-1977; cuid5013 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts (Partial), ca.1977; cuid5014 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Butler, James (Local 420) v. DC 37: Accounting, ca.1979; cuid5015 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, James Butler, 1979; cuid5016 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Lester Wright, 1979; cuid5017 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Lillian Roberts, 1978-1979; cuid5018 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Victor Gotbaum, 1978-1979; cuid5019 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavits, 1979; cuid5020 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavits, Local 420 Members, 1979; cuid5021 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Appellate Division Arguments, Notes, 1979; cuid5022 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Background Materials, 1979; cuid5023 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Charges against DC 37 Members, 1979; cuid5024 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Commission to Take Deposition, 1979; cuid5025 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Constitution and Financial Standards Codes, DC 37 and Local 420, 1971, 1975, 1978; cuid5026 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Depositions, 1979; cuid5027 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Depositions, Local 420 Members, 1979; cuid5028 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Discovery, 1978-1979; cuid5029 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Drafts, ca.1979; cuid5030 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Hospital Crisis and May 1st Rally, 1979; cuid5031 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Local 420 Members' Petition, 1979; cuid5032 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Notes and Research, 1979; cuid5033 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Order to Show Cause, Butler Deposition, 1979; cuid5034 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Order to Show Cause, O'Malley Deposition, 1979; cuid5035 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings I, 1979; cuid5036 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings II, 1979; cuid5037 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings III, 1979; cuid5038 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings IV, 1979; cuid5039 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings V, 1979; cuid5040 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VI, 1979; cuid5041 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VII, 1979; cuid5042 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings VIII, 1979; cuid5043 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings IX, 1979; cuid5044 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings X, 1979; cuid5045 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Pleadings XI, 1979; cuid5046 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Preliminary Injunction, 1979; cuid5047 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Protective Order and Appeal, 1979; cuid5048 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Reply Brief, 1979; cuid5049 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Summary of Argument, ca.1979; cuid5050 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Summaries and Complaint, 1979; cuid5051 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Temporary Restraining Order, 1979; cuid5052 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - City Civil Service Commission, 1982; cuid5053 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement I, 1982-1983; cuid5054 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement II, 1982-1983; cuid5055 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement, Drafts I, 1982-1983; cuid5056 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Deferral Payment Agreement and Comparison Agreement, Drafts II, 1982-1983; cuid5057 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Citywide Bargaining: Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, Drafts, 1982-1983; cuid5058 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Eugene Sanjour Case): Background Materials, 1968-1977; cuid5059 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Correspondence, 1975-1978; cuid5060 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Legal Papers, 1977-1978; cuid5061 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 and CUNY, Board of Higher Education Arbitration (Sanjour Case): Notes, ca.1977; cuid5062 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. New York Police Department (NYPD): Transcripts I, 1980; cuid5063 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts II, 1980; cuid5064 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts III, 1980; cuid5065 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts IV, 1980; cuid5066 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts V, 1980; cuid5067 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 and Local 1549 v. NYPD: Transcripts VI, 1980; cuid5068 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 v. Commission of Investigation of the State of New York (SIC) (Release Time Program Case): Affidavit of Cause, 1981; cuid5069 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, 1973-1981; cuid5070 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, Legal I, undated, 1975; cuid5071 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Background Material, Legal II, undated, 1975; cuid5072 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Correspondence, 1957-1982; cuid5073 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Decision, 1982; cuid5074 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Legal Drafts, undated; cuid5075 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Legal Drafts, 1981; cuid5076 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Memoranda in Opposition, 1981; cuid5077 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Memoranda in Support, 1981; cuid5078 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Compel, Reply Briefs, 1981; cuid5079 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Affidavits in Opposition, 1981; cuid5080 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Affidavits in Support, 1981; cuid5081 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Memoranda in Opposition, 1981; cuid5082 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Motion to Quash, Memoranda in Support, 1981; cuid5083 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Municipal Labor Committee (MLC) Member List, ca.1981; cuid5084 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Order to Show Cause, 1981; cuid5085 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: SIC Annual Reports, 1961-1979; cuid5086 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Subpoenae, 1981; cuid5087 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Transcripts, 1981; cuid5088 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Executive Orders (Mayoral), 1973-1980; cuid5089 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Legal Notes and Memoranda, 1978; cuid5090 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Proposed Legislation I, 1978; cuid5091 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Proposed Legislation II, 1978; cuid5092 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Fiscal Crisis: Effect on Women and Minorities, 1976; cuid5093 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee: DC 37 Merger, 1956-1957; cuid5094 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Background Materials, 1967-1977; cuid5095 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Correspondence, 1977-1978; cuid5096 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Legal Papers, 1977-1978; cuid5097 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Notes, ca.1977; cuid5098 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Transcripts, 1977; cuid5099 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Local 371 (SSEU) v. Adam Walinsky, Chairman of SIC, 1981; cuid5100 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, 1976, 1979; cuid5101 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, Background Materials I, 1957-1980; cuid5102 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, Background Materials II, 1957-1980; cuid5103 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Legal Papers, 1974-1978; cuid5104 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Local 2021 (OTB): Arbitration of Grievance, 1981; cuid5105 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Mando, Daniel J., et al. v. Abraham Beame, et al. (Emergency Employment Act Employees Case): Briefs and Memoranda of Law, 1975; cuid5106 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Mando v. Beame: Correspondence, 1974-1977; cuid5107 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits I, 1971-1974; cuid5108 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits II, 1971-1974; cuid5109 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits III, 1971-1974; cuid5110 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits IV, 1971-1974; cuid5111 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits V, 1971-1974; cuid5112 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Mando v. Beame: Extra Legal, 1974-1976; cuid5113 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Mando v. Beame: Factual, 1971-1974; cuid5114 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Mando v. Beame: Notes and Memoranda, 1974; cuid5115 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings I, 1972-1974; cuid5116 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings II, 1972-1974; cuid5117 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings III, 1972-1974; cuid5118 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Mando v. Beame: Transcripts, 1974; cuid5119 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - MENTOR Program (MELS and Board of Education), 1984; cuid5120 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - MENTOR Program (MELS and Board of Education): Printed Material, undated; cuid5121 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Middlebrooks, et al. v. NYPD (Police Aides Case): Charts and Statistical Analysis, 1976-1979; cuid5122 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Documents and Exhibits, 1978-1980; cuid5123 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Formal Papers, 1980-1981; cuid5124 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Labor-Management Meeting, 1980; cuid5125 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Legal Research, 1975-1979; cuid5126 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Notes, ca.1980; cuid5127 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Statistics on Coverage, 1979; cuid5128 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Witnesses, 1979; cuid5129 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - New York City Board of Education: CETA Titles, 1975; cuid5130 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - New York City Board of Education: Improper Labor Practices, 1976; cuid5131 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - New York City Board of Education: Stavisky-Goodman Litigation, 1976-1980; cuid5132 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation HHC: Conflict of Interest Cases, 1979; cuid5133 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1970-1976; cuid5134 (Box 36, Folder 1)